[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "Test text 1",
        "back": "Test explanation 1"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "Test text 2",
        "back": "Test explanation 2"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "Test text 3",
        "back": "Test explanation 3"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "Test text 4",
        "back": "Test explanation 4"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "Test text 5",
        "back": "Test explanation 5"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "Test text 6",
        "back": "Test explanation 6"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "Test text 7",
        "back": "Test explanation 7"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "Test text 8",
        "back": "Test explanation 8"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "Test text 9",
        "back": "Test explanation 9"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "Test text 10",
        "back": "Test explanation 10"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "Test text 11",
        "back": "Test explanation 11"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "Test text 12",
        "back": "Test explanation 12"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "Test text 13",
        "back": "Test explanation 13"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "Test text 14",
        "back": "Test explanation 14"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "Test text 15",
        "back": "Test explanation 15"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "front": "Test text 16",
        "back": "Test explanation 16"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "front": "Test text 17",
        "back": "Test explanation 17"
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "front": "Test text 18",
        "back": "Test explanation 18"
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "front": "Test text 19",
        "back": "Test explanation 19"
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "front": "Test text 20",
        "back": "Test explanation 20"
    }
]